export const questions = [
    {question: "Do you think YOU suck?",
    answers: [{answer:"No!", value: 0}, {answer:"Not Usually?", value: 1}, {answer:"Sometimes :'(", value:2}, {answer:"Honestly. . . yes", value:3}],
    eggyResponse: "C'mon let's not walk on eggshells here..."},
    {question: "Do you ever find yourself doing embarrassing things?",
    answers: [{answer:"No Way", value: 0} , {answer: "Maybe once when I was a grimy little kid", value: 1} , {answer:"Yes", value: 2}, {answer:"All the time. I'm one clumsy fool", value: 3}],
    eggyResponse: "I know the answer to this question, but do you?"},
    {question: "How often do you get into arguments online?",
    answers: [{answer:"I don't have social media and I never will", value: 0}, {answer:"Maybe I've gotten into a few", value: 1}, {answer:"Like once a month", value: 2}, {answer:"Every. Single. Day", value: 3}],
    eggyResponse: "Translation: how scrambled is your brain?"},
    {question: "Do you lie?",
    answers: [{answer:"I don't do that", value: 0}, {answer:"Just once and I'll regret it for the rest of my miserable life", value: 1}, {answer:"I have before, but I don't make a habit of it", value: 2}, {answer:"Yes. Every day, whenever and to whoever I can", value: 3}],
    eggyResponse: "Have you ever told a parent their baby looks cute? Yeah.... I thought so"},
    {question: "What do you consider to be the most superior egg form?",
    answers: [{answer:"Eggy <3", value: 0}, {answer:"Fried", value: 1}, {answer:"Scrambled", value: 2}, {answer:"I DONT EVEN LIKE EGGS", value: 3}],
    eggyResponse: "See what happens if you don't choose the first option bud"},
    {question: "Favorite frosting?",
    answers: [{answer:"Cream cheese", value: 0}, {answer:"I hate frosting", value: 1}, {answer:"Meringue", value: 2}, {answer:"Buttercream", value: 3}],
    eggyResponse: "While a frosting made from beaten egg whites is terrifying, I find buttercream to be more offensive."},
    {question: "When's the last time you cleaned the device you're taking this quiz on?",
    answers: [{answer:"I use soap and water on it every day", value: 0}, {answer:"About everytime I brush my teeth, so maybe a couple weeks ago?", value: 1}, {answer:"Idk why dont you ask me something actually important", value: 2}, {answer:"Never. This device is nothing more than a petri dish", value: 3}],
    eggyResponse: "Ohhhh so that's why you look so greasy!"},
    {question: "What about your microwave?",
    answers: [{answer:"I don't need to clean something I don't have", value: 0}, {answer:"Once every couple weeks when I forget that tomato sauce is a low-grade explosive", value: 1}, {answer:"The micro waves kill any bacteria, so technically every time I use it", value: 2}, {answer:"Never, I replace my microwave every time I see so much as a splatter", value: 3}],
    eggyResponse: "A microwave sounds so nice and warm!"},
    {question: "Do you use q-tips inside your ear",
    answers: [{answer:"Lol no I would never pose a potential threat to my physical wellbeing", value: 0}, {answer:"What? You've never had a clogged ear before?", value: 1}, {answer:"No comment", value: 2}, {answer:"It's become a compulsion for me", value: 3}],
    eggyResponse: "Maybe one day I'll be able to experience the feeling of ascension associated with q-tip use."},
    {question: "Final question: Do you like cats?",
    answers: [{answer:"YES", value: 0}, {answer:"They're fine", value: 1}, {answer:"Not really", value: 2}, {answer:"I find their indifference to me insulting", value: 3}],
    eggyResponse: "This is the single most important question and the sole determinant of your value as a human being... just FYI"}
  ]